Hello everyone um welcome to this ah tutorial
today we're going to learn about machine learning and uh neural networks
first lets ah talk about the basic concepts of deep learning
neural networks use backpropergation algorithm to train the model um
the algoritm adjusts the weights and biases iteratively
this process ah continues until the loss function is minimized
now lets move on to convolutional neural networks or CNNs
CNNs are particularly good at um image recognition tasks
they use filters to extract features from images ah
finally um lets discuss the training process and optimization